We are Asora-chan!
We are the new art school.
Today we'll be doing this.
Yes!
I would like to make bracelets
I would like to make bracelets!
Oh~!
Cute!!!
But,
Yes!
However,
Yes, yes, yes.
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Suddenly it grazed me
I'm not just making bracelets
Yes, sir
Now, we're going to draw lots.
Yes, sir.
For the members who drew.
I'll make one for you.
I'd like to make it.
Oh~!
So, the member in charge
while not revealing who they are.
the color and shape you prefer,
the color, the shape, and the atmosphere
to create a bracelet design that suits the member
the bracelet design to suit the member's taste.
Ah! I see.
And finally
Which bracelet is made for you?
is the one made for you.
which bracelet is made for you?
Yes, sir.
If you successfully guess the bracelet
You'll be with the member
I guess that means you were cute back then.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's right.
Yes, it was.
Well, let's get right to it.
Let's have a raffle!
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Here we go!
Ta-da!
What do we do now... Yes!
It's destroyed!
Oh no!
I destroyed it. Now there's a hole...
Oh! Yes!
Ta-da!
Gentlemen, come in! Yes!
Bon appétit!
Oh!
This is the gentleman.
Yes!
Here you go, everyone! Yes!
Let's make this one.
We're done! Oh!
Yes! Okay!
Shall we make it? Yes!
Let's go!
Oh!
Let's get to work!
Yeah!
I'm ready!
That's a tough one, the theme of the story.
Wow.
I don't know...
What do you think? What do you think?
Any recent clothing purchases, any special things you're looking for?
What color do you tend to wear?
I didn't write a story. This isn't good.
This, this, this, this, can I take your hand?
I see.
I tend to wear white.
But nowadays, I tend to wear more colors.
Yes, yes, yes.
I want to use colors.
Wow!
I see. Orange?
Yes, that's right.
I have red, green, and various other centers.
I see.
We have a large share of the market.
It's all about color.
What do you think?
Hashige.
I wonder if this is a thread or... what?
I used to wear colored clothes too.
Oh, I see.
Don't like it.
Don't listen to me.
I'm in a lot of pain.
I'm wearing it like this.
Don't like it.
But listen, I'm in the mood.
Are you good at making these?
No, I'm not very good at it.
You're so bad at this.
I'm so bad at it.
We don't have festivals like this.
There was an environmental festival.
It's like a pre-suits festival.
Aww...
Fresh frescos, key chains...
Like this...
Wow...
I don't have any more sense of style.
Anyway, I wanted to put it down as soon as possible.
I don't know...
He says it's his taste.
Oh, hint, hint, hint.
Oh!
Okay.
Nonaka-chan, or rather, you...
You guys...
You...
What kind of shape do you like?
Oh, shape.
Shape?
Uh...
But I think the shape of this flower is really cute.
I mean...
Oh!
Ooh...
It's a real beauty powerhouse.
LOL!
I don't know. You like glitter so much.
It's kind of a must.
I don't know.
I like glitter.
Oh, really?
Sparkles.
I used to collect beads like this when I was a student.
I used to collect them all the time.
Right?
There are so many cute ones lately.
They're cute.
What? I don't think so.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Matt glitter?
I'm more of a glitter kind of girl.
I like the glitter better.
You know, from a while ago, from a while ago, from a while ago...
Oh, I don't know. Tree glitter.
Sparkling tree.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
I think I'm more interested in the sparkling tree.
Oh, that's right.
I'm starting to get suspicious of Sakuraya.
Yeah, something's up.
I'm suspicious.
He keeps asking the same people.
That's true.
Everyone... everyone asked.
Laughs.
And I'm just kind of...
Uh...
Aww.
Cute.
Get on your butt.
Eh, lol.
Bite head.
Laughs.
Bite-head.
Do you like butts?
The butt.
LOL!
If you had to choose between cold and warm colors, which would you prefer?
Uh huh.
But I think I might be liking colder colors lately.
Like light blue.
I used to like bright colors a lot.
I like yellow.
Blue is also cute.
I've got a thing for blue, too.
Oh...
I like cold colors, too.
I like cold colors.
Oh...
Everyone likes cold colors.
Everybody likes cold colors.
Me too.
Oh, great.
Cold or masculine...
I like light colors.
Oh, wow.
That's true.
Pastel colors
Light blue
Certainly.
And...
Pastel colors
Blue to
Blue
Pastel colors
Do any color combinations fit again?
I like blue keys.
Oh, I see.
Uh...
Uh-huh.
I don't know.
It was a lot of fun, so I'm a little freaked out.
I'm a little worried.
It's a really small one.
The one that falls off.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Shinkasuka.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I used to do that when I was just a little girl.
There were all these colored rubber bands.
Like bracelets that you weave together.
Oh, that's right.
I don't know...
something like this...
It's like this.
Here's something...
Oh, knit it.
Heh.
You did a lot of work.
It takes so much time.
It's amazing.
I was having so much fun doing it.
Heh.
I'm glad you're doing it too.
I'm relieved.
Yeah, I'm sure.
And...
Nerves
Yeah.
But if it goes over my stomach...
Home?
I mean...
She's asleep, right?
How much?
About five.
It's a little difficult.
Difficult
It's difficult.
You like bracelets?
That's a tough one.
That's difficult.
That's a hard one.
That's hard.
Difficult
It's hard it's hard it's really hard it's really hard
It's difficult
I feel like
I'll get you another one.
What's the mood of the moon chart?
I'm in the mood for moon chart
I love comments
Camera
I turned my back to the camera.
Oh, I can see your backs.
Oh, there, guys.
They look alike, they look alike.
Blue-ish.
You're right.
I said they're all monochromatic.
Don't pick again.
Oh, I don't have that one.
Is that possible?
Tell him he can open it.
Oh, it's open.
Do I need to think about the design of this one anymore?
Whatever you want.
I'll do it however I want.
That's right.
And if you think about it, you'll feel it.
It's all right if you have the feeling if you think
I have that too.
Gentlemen.
How did you spend the New Year's Eve?
How did I spend it?
And did you get to see the big show?
Oh, yes, I did.
It was really fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I thought what you said was really funny.
No, I don't think Emba will cry there.
I don't think Emba will cry anymore.
No way.
You didn't think I couldn't tell you in the audience, did you?
Yes, I did.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's right.
Oh, no.
Really.
Tomorrow is Christmas Aid.
Yeah.
Oh.
Tomorrow is Christmas Aid.
That's right.
Well, how is everyone spending their Christmas Aid?
Christmas Aid.
Rehearsals and stuff.
Right.
Rehearsals.
Oh, but I...
I thought it was tomorrow.
It's Christmas aide, so...
This is the day.
I'm going out for pancakes.
You're going to eat pancakes?
I'm going.
Oh, that's nice.
I've been going by this place.
The pancakes at the coffee shop look delicious.
But when I asked my mom to go, she said no.
So I'll go alone.
Sounds scary.
Do you sleep late during holidays?
Or do you go out at night?
Do you go out at home?
Maybe I go out.
I go to my grandma's house.
Every year, we have a song for 31.
And then we started broadcasting the Kansai Devil movie.
After that...
I used to play Baton.
Every year we would go to Hatsumode with the kids from that age group.
It's really nice.
You're still going to do it in 2024.
That's a lot of people.
That's right.
I've always lived at home.
My life is at home.
I've been doing this for a while now.
I don't mind at all.
Vegetables.
I'd like to go there.
There's a lot of them out there.
I go every year for the first time.
Wow!
You said that last year.
Go early in the morning.
With friends.
You go with friends?
I like variety shows on TV during the New Year's holidays.
I wake up unusually early and watch them all the time.
I recommend you don't go to sleep until soon.
I'm up late.
Late.
You mean you don't sleep much?
Almost all day.
That's why I sleep at night and stay up all night.
In the morning I'm up before it starts.
Wow! Wow!
Not exactly healthy.
That's great.
I know, right?
It's funny, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'll make it.
It's amazing.
It's a thin little thing.
It's not expensive at all.
Here you go.
You'll need a lot.
It takes a lot.
Thanks to the staff.
I'm home.
In my stomach
Sleeps a lot
Lots of sleeping
What's the food you've been into lately?
I ate the mar-a-la-tang I promised Noka earlier.
I ate it before you.
But then the ma lah tang stopped.
I wanted to go back tomorrow.
The kind where you choose your own ingredients?
Yes.
If you choose too many, the price is too high.
That's my theory.
The soup and vermicelli alone is 690 yen.
The ingredients are added on top of that.
We don't charge 1,500 yen for ingredients.
1,500 yen.
It's only about 400 yen for both of us!
That's great!
Usually these days...
What's that?
Yogurt, banana and frozen fruit.
Wow!
There's so much of it.
What should I do?
What's that?
Just start from the beginning.
I don't know, it just didn't work.
I had a good feeling when I was choosing the beets.
But when I actually put them in.
I felt like these beats weren't in the right order.
I had to redo it.
You thought the girl ate them.
It's love.
I used to do crafts and stuff when I was little.
If you've been doing crafts since you were a little girl...
I see.
I really have no taste.
Every day in home economics.
Like making bags and stuff.
Yeah.
Did we make bags?
I don't remember.
Your memory is like Ishii's.
Ishii's method.
Ishii wash with water.
Colorful every day
Bubbles, bubbles, bubbles, bubbles, bubbles, bubbles...
The end
It's done, isn't it?
That's great!
It's so cute!
That's great.
Who's looking at theirs?
Look.
Look at that.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
The way you were talking about the information...
Is that right?
Is that what's coming?
You're a good listener.
I like leaving you alone.
I don't know.
It's easy to understand.
How's that?
Absolutely.
So-so, so-so.
Yeah. - Yeah?
What?
Am I right?
No, it means he's good.
Whoever made Emma.
I mean, he's good at hiding it.
He's good.
What about a yukata?
Can't you wear one?
Yes, I can.
I'm sure the home economics department will have you do that.
Do you like big patterns?
Or do you like small patterns?
Do you like a lot of patterns?
Maybe they wear big, loud patterns.
Maybe she wears big, loud patterns.
Oh, really?
Yeah. - Really?
Flashy? What do you think?
What's she like?
What do you think?
What do you mean?
What about someone like Yuuka?
You like flashy?
You like fancy?
Some big shells, some small shells.
Oh, I see.
What do you like now?
What about Emma?
How's Emma?
Emma is, but she's fancy, too.
That's great. That's great. I noticed.
Me too. But I like flashy.
I see. So it's like everyone likes flashy.
I see.
I don't even need a big one. I like small, colorful, or flashy ones.
Cute and glamorous like that.
Tiny and cute.
I like it.
Oh, I can say that, can't I?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, then?
Like this.
It looks good, doesn't it?
Yeah, I think it's cute.
This way, right? I think that's better.
This guy... Emma only sees one person now.
She only sees one good guy.
Oh, but what do you think?
Oh, it's different.
It's pretty great.
I think it would be good to know if you're a head or something right now.
I recommend it with a man and a girl.
You can't wear that.
It's absolutely impossible.
Yes, you can.
So take off the knife.
Heh heh heh.
That's amazing!
It's going to be amazing!
If you do it like that, it's like, "Bjorn!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Sorry.
Phew!
Yes, it's done!
It's done!
Now, please explain the presslet that each one of you made,
say a few words to the person who will receive it.
Let's start with me.
I think I'll go with something pretty and pink,
Oh, cute!
Something pastel,
I was thinking.
I used to wear something like that.
Oh!
I used to wear something like this.
The scissors are like this.
I used cold colors,
I added yellow and pink in places,
I didn't want it to be too cold,
I made them a little brighter,
I added a lot of tiny little things,
I added a lot of tiny little things to make it sparkle!
Oh, cute!
So cute!
This is how I did it.
Oh!
Um, a little more white,
In that,
White?
What is it?
It's a little bit of a point,
I used this slightly cooler shade of blue,
I used it.
Yes.
Well, I think the swab will be..,
I thought, "Well, I think Swab must be like this,
I had an image of him wearing this kind of clothes,
So I used it.
Oh!
Next, Rinna-san.
Hi.
I also said that I like cold colors,
So I added some cold colors,
I also have an image of colorful clothes,
Oh!
I added some green and yellow to it,
I added some green and yellow to make it colorful.
Oooh!
So, I made it colorful,
So, which bracelet was made by me?
I'll go ahead and do it now.
Se-no!
Yes!
Oh, great, great, great!
Oh, wow!
Oh, great!
Next time, I'm Yuna!
Oh!
made it.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'll be there. I am for Riko-chan!
Oh!
I made it.
I made one for Nono-chan!
Yes, I did.
I made it for Eno-chan!
I made it.
Oh!
Shall we give them as presents, then, everyone!
Yes!
For both of you!
All right, then,
Okay, thank you.
Not at all, not at all,
Yes.
Thank you!
Cute!
Let's make it!
Yikes.
Cute!
Black!
It's so good with the colorful knit!
I really like it!
It goes with pastels.
Yeah.
It's so cute!
The student is doing the best,
For sure!
Sure!
Yes!
How do you like the seasonal images?
Were they easy to make?
Yes!
It was easy for me too.
Really?
With the image of SHIRO?
Yes!
When you said you like colorful things these days,
I thought, "Oh, no! I thought, "Oh, no!
But..,
But...
It's easy to make.
I was pretty aware of what I was doing.
It was easy to understand.
I'm not really good with puppet techniques.
It was fun.
That's how we all did it.
Is that what you do?
That's what you do.
And you're not very good at fooling people.
We got it?
Pierre.
Well, that's it.
That's all for now... I made shrimp tube bracelets.
Please leave a comment!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!
Reborn now!